恭喜你完成了这个短期课程，感谢你的参与。
Congratulations and thank you for getting to the end of this short course.
在课程结束之际，让我们回顾一下我们所涵盖的主要话题：
As we conclude the course, let's recap the main topics we covered.
我们详细了解了LM的工作原理，包括诸如分词器之类的细微之处，以及为什么它无法将单词lollipop中的字符翻转。
We went over details of how an LM works, including subtleties like the tokenizer and why it can't reverse lollipop.
我们学习了评估用户输入的方法，以确保系统的质量和安全，
We learned methods for evaluating user inputs to ensure the quality and safety of the system,
使用思维链推理和链式Prompt将任务切分成子任务来处理输入，并在将结果展示给用户之前检查输出。
processing inputs using both chain of thought reasoning and splitting tasks into subtasks with chain prompts and checking outputs before showing them to users.
我们还研究了随着时间的推移评估系统的方法，以监控和提升其性能。
We also took a look at methods for evaluating the system over time, so as to monitor and improve its performance.
在整个课程中，我们也讨论了负责任地使用这些工具的重要性，
Throughout the course, we also discussed the importance of building responsibly with these tools,
确保模型安全，提供准确、相关，且符合你期望的语调的回答。
ensuring that the model is safe and provides appropriate responses that are accurate, relevant, and in the tone you want.
一如既往，实践是掌握这些概念的关键，所以我们希望你能在自己的项目中应用你所学到的知识。
As always, practice is key to mastering these concepts, so we hope you'll apply what you've learned in your own projects.
就是这样。
And so that's it.
还有许多令人兴奋的应用等待着你去开发。
There are so many exciting applications that are yet to be built.
世界需要更多像你这样的人去构建有价值的应用，
The world needs more people like you building useful applications,
我们期待看到你创造出的了不起的作品。
and we look forward to hearing about the amazing things you build.